### **ABOUT ME**

Passionate about UX design and actively learning its principles and techniques. With a technical support and troubleshooting background, I've sharpened my eye for detail and problem-solving. Excited to apply my skills in creating exceptional user experiences. Let's collaborate and make great things happen!

### CONTACT

- Mahtabbeiki@gmail.com
- www.mahtabbeiki.com
- 0645222413
- Rotterdam, Netherlands

### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Computer Networks Engineering

### **SKILLS**

- User Experience Design
- User Interface Design
- Design Thinking
- HTML/CSS
- Midjourney
- Leonardo Ai

### **CERTIFICATES**

- User Experience Foundation
  The Interaction Foundation Design Jan 2023
- Figma UI UX Design Essentials
  Udemy Apr 2023
- Design Thinking
  Growth tribe ongoing

# Mahtab Beiki

### UI/UX DESIGNER

I am passionate about designing digital experiences that are both visually stunning and intuitive, and always strive to create designs that delight and engage users.

### **EXPERIENCE**

UX GYM BOOTCAMP - BONANZA DESIGN GMBH April 2023 - Jul 2023

I enrolled in a comprehensive UX design program, guided by experienced mentors, to enhance my skills. I developed a strong foundation in problem-solving, wireframing, and prototyping, and gained a deep understanding of hierarchy and element positioning for effective product design.

## INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY ADMINSTRATOR - HEXOSYS SDN BHD

Feb 2020 - Dec 2021

In my IT administration role, I maintained the company's website, set up an internal wiki, managed network servers, monitored performance, troubleshooted issues, ensured security, supported users, and communicated with vendors to assure seamless operations.

### NETWORK OPERATION CENTER ENGINEER - SEPANTA Jul 2018 - Apr 2019

IT SUPPORT ADMINISTRATOR - HNG May 2017 – Jun 2018

**CUSTOMER SERVICE SPECIALIST - PTE** Sep 2016 – May 2017